Thank you for sharing your responses on the forum. Now,
非常感谢你能在论坛上分享你的回答 现在
in writing all of this code, we've seen a lot of
在写所有这些代码时 我们已经看到了许多
new words. Let's review all of them. So here I
新词 让我们复习一下 那么 这里是我将
have both of my programming files on the screen at the
两个程序文件同时显示在屏幕上
same time. Here's my first programming file where I'm making
在我的第一个程序文件中我创建了
the class movie. And the second one, when I'm defining instances
类 movie 接着在第二个文件中 我定义那个类的
of that class, instances like Toy Story and Avatar. Now, you
实例 例如 toy_story 和 acatar 现在 你
may have to go into Full Screen mode to be able
可能需要打开全屏模式以便
to read all of the details on the screen.
看清屏幕上的所有细节
Okay, let's start reviewing all of the new words.
好的 让我们开始复习所有遇到的新词
So, we started out by defining a class. The
所以 我们从定义一个类开始
class Keyword allows us to make classes. You can think
class 关键字使我们创建类 你可以将
of a class as a blueprint. And a class
类看作是蓝图 并且类
can have both data and methods. Now, we can
可以同时有数据和方法 现在 我们可以
create multiple instances of a class. In this case,
创建类的多个实例 在这个例子中
we created instances like Toy Story and Avatar. We could
我们创建的实例为 toy_story 和 avatar 我们能
have created many more. Now, when we create
创建更多 现在 当我们创建
an instance of a class, instance like Toy
一个类的实例 如 toy_story
Story, the classes constructor gets called. This is
类的构造函数被调用 这个
essentially the init method inside the class. It is
实质上就是类中的 init 函数 它
here that we initialize all of the data
是我们初始化所有与实例有关
associated with the instance. The constructor uses the keyword,
的数据的地方 构造函数使用关键字
self. Now, you can think of self as
self 现在 你可以认为 self 是
itself or the instance in question. So, when the
自身或者被牵涉的实例 那么 当
instance Toy Story is getting created, self is
实例 toy_story 被创建时 self 是
Toy Story. All the variables associated with a specific
toy_story 所有与一个具体实例有关的变量
instance are called instance variables. Now, these are
被叫做实例变量 现在 这些变量对于
unique to an object and can be accessed using
一个对象来说是独特 并且他们可被类中的 self
the self keyword inside the class and the
关键字及类之外的实例名称
instance name outside the class. And, finally, all of
所访问 另外 最后
the functions inside the class that are associated
类中所有与实例有关的函数 它们都
with an instance and have the first argument as
拥有 self 作为第一个参数 这些函数
self are called instance methods. So there you have it. All of the
被称为实例方法 那么到此你应该理解了
new words that we have learned thus far, right there on one screen.
屏幕上目前我们所学到的所有的新词